{
    "id": "55c3f9b8c14f4144819ad18834e45fd2",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": ".................................... like hamburgers.",
            "description": "All + noun cannot be the subject of a negative verb. Instead we write ‘not all + noun + affirmative verb’.",
            "answers": [
                "Not all Americans",
                "All Americans do not"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1ff5dc947e894dd4ab155b1441228497"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have been round ............................ looking for my puppy.",
            "description": "The expression ‘all the village’ means every part of the village. ",
            "answers": [
                "every village",
                "all the village"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0008673b6ae544538389142c6bb2388b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Susie spent .................................. at home.",
            "description": "The article should go before whole.",
            "answers": [
                "whole week",
                "whole the week",
                "the whole week"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0fbe9f7523e34c58be2d8faf2adc1d60"
        },
        {
            "question": "I spent ................................ at home.",
            "description": "The article goes after all.",
            "answers": [
                "all the day",
                "the all day",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f6405615f5a644b88186d9e4b815e0ff"
        },
        {
            "question": "My dog understands every word I say – he is ............................ human.",
            "description": "Almost can mean ‘similar to but not exactly the same’. Nearly is not used with this meaning. ",
            "answers": [
                "almost",
                "nearly",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e8f2148474174ab7a3d0a5c2e0ea3884"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ............................ wish I had accepted the invite.",
            "description": "Almost can mean ‘similar to but not exactly the same’. Nearly is not used with this meaning. ",
            "answers": [
                "almost",
                "nearly",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "422f9bcf48c944608474678a300068af"
        },
        {
            "question": ".............................. nobody came.",
            "description": "Nearly cannot be used before negative words.",
            "answers": [
                "Almost",
                "Nearly",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bc701b05860b4331a66fe555e219a8da"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have just read ............................. Brothers Karamazov.",
            "description": "Before proper nouns all of and the whole of are both possible.",
            "answers": [
                "the whole of",
                "all of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "508932da908c4ef9b5bfcf10f209479c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Students are not ................................. to park here.",
            "description": "The verbs allowed and permitted can both be used in passive structures.",
            "answers": [
                "allowed",
                "permitted",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8c045440767842dca61b3757a4bcd60b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wasn’t .............................. to enter the club.",
            "description": "Let is not used in the passive.",
            "answers": [
                "allowed",
                "let",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ad1a3702d3074281ad496c09384f0c5d"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘She is kind.’ ‘Her sister is .............................’",
            "description": "We do not normally use also in short answers.",
            "answers": [
                "as well",
                "also",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2b071d1883154625b7147de1f47bf53d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please give me some rice ............................",
            "description": "Also is not normally used in imperatives.",
            "answers": [
                "as well",
                "also",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1a75d49adefc4c29b440f4798513b14b"
        }
    ]
}